A Guide to the Friends of Nelson Record of the Western and Central Virginia Resistance to the Atlantic Coast Pipeline, 2014-2021
Library of Virginia
- Photographs, 2014-2020 (Box 11)
  This series contains an index of photographs taken by Eleanor Amidon.
  - Photographs index--Eleanor Amidon, 2014-2020 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Pipes, Pipe Yards, and Storage (Box 11)
  This series includes information on the coating of pipes and on their storage.
  - Pipe yards and storage areas (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Safety and Public Health, 2014-2015 (Box 11)
  In letters to the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission (FERC) and other agencies and officials, as well as in public relations and tabling materials, citizens and groups raised concerns about the blast radius for a potential pipeline failure, about safety issues related to blasting during pipeline construction, as well as about public health issues related to the pipeline.
  - Papers, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Resources for Researching Public Health Implications of the Atlantic Coast Pipeline for Nelson County, VA, by Sheila Stone December 2014 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Surveys, 2014-2015 (Box 11)
  This series includes materials from landowners on their resistance to Dominion's efforts to survey land along the proposed route of the Atlantic Coast Pipeline. There is correspondence from Dominion, from landowners, from landowner lawyers, and from Dominion lawyers, as well as general materials about the surveys and about landowner rights.
  - Dominion surveys--Ronald Enders and Ellen Bouton, 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Dominion surveys--Steven and Ann Majewski, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Dominion surveys--John Ed and Ruth Purvis, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Dominion surveys--John Ed and Ruth Purvis, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Dominion surveys--Philip Purvis, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Dominion surveys--Quinn and Laura Robinson, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Dominion surveys--Martin and Katherine Versluys, 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Dominion surveys--Samuel Woodson, 2015 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Oversize materials (Box 12 and 1-6)
  This series includes yard signs, informational display boards used in tabling, banners used for tabling and demonstrations, and one reusable shopping bag.
  - !Enough Is Enough! Give Back Our Stolen Democracy Land Air Water Friends of Buckingham banner--70 1/2" x 45 1/4" (Friends of Buckingham) (Box 12)
  - Stolen: Our Land Air Water and Lives Union Hill Resists Friends of Buckingham VA Concern 4 the New Generation banner--69 1/2" x 44 1/2" (Box 12)
  - Our Community Won banner--59 1/2" x 23 1/4" (Box 12)
  - Dominion Atlantic Coast Pipeline reusable shopping bag (Box 12)
  - No Pipeline yard sign (both sides)--24" x 18" (Folder 1)
  - Property Rights Revival Rockfish Valley Community Center Sunday 11/6 2 PM yard sign (both sides)--24" x 18" (Folder 1)
  - No Pipeline ALLPAINNOGAIN.com yard sign (both sides)--26" x 16" (Folder 1)
  - Dominion Global Warming Starts Here yard sign--24" x 18" (Folder 1)
  - And Dominion Calls This an Environmentally Responsible Route for the Atlantic Coast Pipeline??!! and on reverse Harris Cove poster--29 1/2 x 20" (Folder 2)
  - Impact of Eastern Alternative Route to Wetlands Peavine Area poster--30" x 20" (Folder 2)
  - Friends of Nelson ACP in Nelson County poster--36" x 25 3/4" (Folder 3)
  - Proposed Atlantic Coast Pipeline, MVP and Other Pipelines poster 40" x 30" (Folder 4)
  - Imagine the Loss. Don't Buy Dominion's Propaganda. listing myth versus fact poster--42" x 30" (Folder 5)
  - Imagine the Loss. Don't Buy Dominion's Propaganda. 'The Atlantic Coast Pipeline Will Change Everything and Nothing.' Says Who?! (Dominion, of course!) poster--41 3/4" x 30" (Folder 6)